- Hey, how'd you sleep, Peter?
- Brian, last night I had this crazy dream.
I was eating a sheep
and now my pillow's gone.
Oh, wait. Here it is.
What the hell was I eating?
Oh, sorry.
See you, Lois.
And like I tell you every day, if I come
back in the middle of the afternoon
and you're having sex with somebody,
I'll kill you both.
"Thanks to effective treatments,
Magic Johnson down to one AID."
Oh, God, did I hit that deaf kid again?
They ought to put a bell on that guy.
The nurse says Brian won't be out
of surgery for another three hours.
- Oh, I hope he's gonna be okay.
- Me, too.
I know we're not here to place blame
or beat ourselves up, but,
I can't help feeling like
this is somehow Meg's fault.
Oh, I just can't stand the thought
of losing Brian.
If he dies, I'm gonna have
to start hanging out with The Rock again.
One's a baby,
and the other's black, I think.
At least part black. Or Hispanic.
I think, you know, possibly,
there's some Filipino in there.
Yeah, possibly some Filipino.
I mean, if he, if he's black,
it's definitely diluted.
I mean, one of his parents must be white.
What the hell is Jessica Alba,
for that matter?
If I were 40 years younger,
I would plow that till next July.
All right, class, today as a special treat,
I'm going to show you this
fascinating episode of NOVA
that I taped at home for you.
You coming back to bed, Rob?
Hang on, honey. Hang on.
My jaw keeps locking up.
Well, that's not NOVA at all, is it?
That's a sex tape I made with my wife.
Of course, nobody here is interested
in seeing that sort of thing.
Are they? Probably not. No.
Okay. You kind of looked like
you were nodding? Nope?
Okay. Okay, we should get back to work.
All right, next up,
does everyone have a lab partner?
- I don't.
- Me, neither.
She can be my partner.
Sarah, that's very irresponsible.
Meg is awful.
- You want to be my lab partner?
- Really?
Sure, you seem nice.
Hey, do you want
to join my after-school club?
Sure.
Now, open your books to page...
You know what? Look, I'm sorry.
Can I just go ahead and show this video
of me doing my wife?
Here we are, Brian, safe and sound.
- Peter, I don't need to be in a wheelchair.
- Now, now, no arguments, Brian.
I already went through the trouble
of borrowing this ramp from Joe.
I'll see you, honey. I'll be back in a...
Joe, are you all right?
Don't help me up.
I need to retain my independence.
- You need anything from the market?
- PowerBar!
What's wrong, Brian?
You've just been sitting on the couch
ever since you got back from the hospital.
You need to get out of the house.
I don't know, Lois. I'm a little depressed.
The accident got me thinking
about how uncertain life is
and how suddenly it can be taken away.
You're going to feel back to normal
in no time.
- Here, have some food.
- I'm not hungry.
Here comes the gravy.
You messy beast.
Well, hello there, Meg.
Neil, I really can't be seen talking
to you anymore.
I have friends now,
and some of them, very popular.
I know. I heard Sarah is your lab partner.
All those years of you rejecting me
finally made sense.
What do you mean?
Oh, my God!
Meg! There you are.
Hey, everybody,
this is our newest member, Meg.
- Hi, Meg.
- What's up?
Hi, you gays, guys. Girls.
Look, listen, Sarah, I can't be in your club.
I'm not a lesbian.
You can't be serious.
We had a whole party planned for you.
Really? A party, for me?
- But I guess if you're not a lesbian...
- Wait, wait.
You didn't let me finish. I'm not a lesbian.
I'm a super, huge mega-lesbian.
Good.
You'll fit in with the other mega-lesbians.
Wow! I feel so socially accepted.
Hey, do you have any other friends
you want to invite to your party?
No. Most of my friends are out of town.
Oh, this is gonna be great!
We'll stay up late, trade stories.
Let's watch the video of my ballet recital.
Here it is!
Sunshine Bear. Wait!
- Hey, how's it going?
- Good.
Those are huge.
Those are huge boobs.
And you know what's nice?
That you don't have that blue vein
up there that some of the bigger ones get.
What? I said you don't have that.
- Hey, buddy, you're not looking so good.
- Who cares how I look? Nothing matters.
We could all die tomorrow,
every one of us.
Well, isn't that a damn good reason
to live it up today?
- Come on, it can't possibly be that simple.
- Excuse me. I got a thing to do.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
we have a very special guest tonight.
Please welcome the Member of the Board,
Frank Sinatra Jr.
All this singing is contagious. I'll sing, too.
A little bit softer now.
I'll come out when they're all gone.
Wow, Brian, you actually got
to sing with Frank Sinatra Jr?
Oh, it was amazing.
I got to tell you, he said some things
that were exactly what I needed to hear,
and I was just inspired
to get up on that stage.
Got to live life for today, you know?
Brian, don't you think it's a little too early
to be hitting the booze?
Hey, what's the point of waiting?
You got to live life while you can
and live it hard.
The Chris Farley method, that's good.
Frank invited me back this evening.
I tell you, I feel more exhilarated than
Peter did when he swam with the bulls.
Yeah, that's fair.
No, that's totally a fair score.
You know, Brian, when you wear that suit,
it looks like you're taking a white poop.
But it's stuck.
Look, Lois asked me to baby-sit you,
so just stay here and be quiet.
I'll be back after my first set.
What the hell am I supposed
to do to kill time?
Oh, maybe I'll play 52 Pickup.
This game's better
if there's someone else here.
'Cause then they can say,
"I'm not going to pick up those cards. "
And then I say,
"You have to, it's 52 Pickup. "
And they say,
"Well, what if I just leave them there?"
And I say, " Those are my father's cards.
You can't just leave them there.
"He's going to be mad. "
Where am I?
Get out of here.
Whoa. Easy, kid. These people paid
good money to get in here.
Oh, yeah? How much
are you charging them to get out?
That was sensational.
We're going to be the biggest thing
since Edison harnessed electricity.
Look at Edison over there
with his damn electricity.
Hey, Edison, how about sharing some
of those light bulbs, huh?
- Hey, figure it out for yourself, man.
- We're freezing our asses off over here.
Hey, man, how do you think I feel,
you know?
You get to look at my great house.
I get to look at that dark thing, huh?
What, what is that, a candle over there?
That's pretty sweet.
Yeah, it's a candle.
We're freezing over here.
No one in my family's taken a bath
in a month. We stink.
It stinks over here, you jerk.
I can't hear you over my central heating.
- Hey, why don't you go to hell, Edison.
- Hey, bite me, man.
Hey, you guys seen The Office?
Oh, no, I guess you haven't
'cause you don't have a TV.
Hey, how about I come over there
and kick your ass?
Yeah, come on over.
- What is this, Lois?
- It's jambalaya. It's a new recipe.
Peter. Eat your food, mister.
All right, if you don't want it,
put it in your napkin.
Peter, put it in your napkin!
Put it in your...
I'm not gonna...
You know, some people would
be very happy to have this food.
Like John Goodman's family.
Please, Daddy.
I told you, when I'm finished,
you can have what's left.
There won't be any left.
There's never any left.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Mom, why is the cable guy here?
It's me, you guys,
and I have something to tell you all.
Mom. Dad. I am a lesbian.
- That is awesome.
- Peter.
Meg, you are not a lesbian.
You know, I don't care
what you guys think.
All my new lesbian friends accept me,
and that's all that matters.
Meg, you're my daughter.
I would accept you if you were gay
or blind or retarded, but you're not.
You guys don't care about me
and my struggle! I hate you!
Meg, I think you're just trying to fit in
by pretending to be something you're not.
Like the time Peter pretended
to be racist to get out of jury duty.
Awful lot of honkies in here.
Brian, there you are.
Do you have any idea what time it is?
Stewie was supposed
to be in bed two hours ago.
Oh, yeah, he... He's...
He was right here,
right next to me like, four hours ago.
What? Brian,
you were supposed to watch him!
- Oh, my little sweetie!
- Hey, Brian, remember me?
I'm the guy you left standing
at the counter
at McDonald's with a bag full of burgers.
You know, it's funny,
I tried to walk home and...
A lot of hungry deer walking around
at this hour of the night and...
Oh, here's where the story gets fun.
You may have noticed I'm missing an ear.
Managed to pull it out of the deer's mouth
and put it in some ice I got at a 7-Eleven.
So, when you're ready to apologize,
just talk into this cup.
Brian, this is inexcusable.
Yeah, what if something
had happened to Stewie?
My ear's in a cup,
I guess that doesn't count.
Hey, I'm not the kid's baby-sitter,
all right? I have my own life to live.
You know, this is all because you've been
hanging out with that Frank Sinatra Jr.
I am gonna call his mother Mia Farrow
and give her a piece of my mind.
And you are gonna stop singing
at that crazy club.
- Operator, Mia Farrow, please.
- You stay out of my life!
What the hell is happening to you?
Yeah, don't worry, I don't need to go
to the hospital or anything.
I'll just use this Mr. Potato Head piece.
- He bit me, Lois. The bastard bit me.
- Oh, honey, I'm sure he didn't mean it.
Brian's going through some heavy stuff
right now. He almost died.
Listen, Peter, I...
I just want to apologize.
You know what? Forget it.
I don't need this.
I'm out of here.
Look what you did, Peter.
I can't help it. I haven't been this scared
since I was mugged by Gene Shalit.
Don't Panic Room.
I'm not going to William Hurt you.
I only want your Tango & Cash.
So just Pay It Forward
and we'll all be Happy Gilmore.
What?
So, how's my suddenly
lesbian daughter doing?
Great. We're checking out naked girls.
I am so into girls.
Oh, come on, Meg,
you can stop the charade.
My God, you're as transparent
as your father was
when he pretended to be
a Hasidic Jew to get off work.
Good morning, Hebrews and shebrews.
What a glorious Jewish day.
Hey, how about all those coupons
in the Sunday paper, huh?
Some good deals there.
Hey, you know, I went into a store
last week and they wanted $800 for a TV,
but I us'ed them down to $500.
It's not a charade, Mom. I am a lesbian.
What do I have to do to prove this to you?
Well, maybe if I'd seen you
kiss your girlfriend.
- Fine.
- What was that?
What is she, your grandmother?
That's no kiss. Watch this.
Look, I can't tell you how to lead your life.
If you don't want to face the truth,
there's nothing I can do about it.
Chris, I'm all out of digital audio tape.
Oh, he's gone.
Hey, can I get you guys
to sign these release forms?
- Oh, where the hell is Brian?
- I don't know, but I better go find him.
We can't sit here watching
infomercials all night.
Hello. How come I rich and you not?
How come you not sell real estate
like I do?
How come I sleep with your wife
while you at work
and then I pee in your toilet
and don't flush?
And sometimes I open the back part and
I pee in there, so that when you flush
pee come out. You know why?
Because I'm smart.
I'm smart, you're stupid. Call now.
Brian! Brian!
Brian! Brian...
Who am I kidding? All those buttons,
I'll look like Steve Harvey. Brian!
Yeah, I'll ask the cashier
if I can put this up in the window.
I definitely need a breath freshener.
But that's going to give me 11 items.
- That's fine.
- No, no, no.
Rules is rules.
Let's see what I'm gonna put back.
Okay, I need the Reynolds Wrap
and the bathroom tissue.
I could do without the Triscuits,
but they sure are good.
7- Up's the whole reason I came down here
in the first place. You know what?
I'm not gonna need the V8,
because I can just get some tomato juice
at the mini-mart down the street.
It's a little more expensive,
but that's okay.
I like to help out a small business.
I hope it's okay if I pay you in pennies.
Oh, God, a gutter? How clichй.
I don't know what went wrong.
I was just trying to live for the moment,
you know?
Because life can end so abruptly
and there's nothing you can do to stop it.
Is that why you've been on this path
to self-destruction?
You know, Brian, as smart as you are,
you've got to accept the fact that
there are some things in life
that you just can't control.
You mean the way, the way
you can't control that messed up way
that you laugh when you think
something's really, really funny?
Well, Hope, I don't understand why
these cookies are giving us all the fits.
Well, no wonder, Faith.
That's not baking powder.
It's sneezing powder.
But, I already brought a whole batch
to the church bake sale.
No wonder that priest kept saying,
'"Bless you. '"
Yes, and I accept that.
Your problem is, you think that
just because you're not in control,
nothing matters. That you don't matter.
But you know what?
You matter to someone.
You matter big time.
Hey, Meg. What are you doing here?
Listen, Sarah,
I got to get something off my chest.
- Yes!
- I need to open up.
- Sweet.
- So get ready 'cause here it is.
- My mom was right.
- What do you mean?
- I'm not gay.
- What?
So, all those rounds of golf we played,
those were all lies?
I'm so sorry.
For the first time in my life,
I felt like I belonged,
and I wanted it to be true.
So I pretended to be something I'm not.
You're going to choose
to be heterosexual?
- I thought being gay wasn't a choice.
- Well, not for guys.
It was wrong of me to mislead you.
I should go.
That was awful. That was just awful.
What do you think, Mark?
I don't know, man.
We didn't get the shots we need.
Man, what do you think, Mike?
I mean, if you saw action going on
in front of you,
would you know instinctively
to center it in front of you?
I don't know. Could someone take
my soda out of the icebox please,
so it doesn't freeze?
- Frank, there you are.
- Mia Farrow?
What's this I hear about you up all night
with a baby and a dog?
Oh, leave me alone.
Get over here, young man.
Damn it all.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru